Could you go to sleep at 7:19 PM
?
Nothing I'd like more. I'm
extremely
tired right now anyway, so let's go.
I
started my evening routine at 2:30 pm because I still had to do
laundry, as I
had overslept that morning.  I hate doing
housework in the evenings.
My evening routine is sacred to me.
Holy.  I think this is the
first vlog that has a bit of an autumnal feel
.  It had been raining
all day, it was
chilly, so I went into the
bathtub.  I'm so excited for
autumn, aren't I?  You can't
imagine it.  For me, autumn really starts
in September, but
somehow I'm already in the mood for it this year
.  I can
start decorating right now.  But I'm going
away for a few days this week, so I had to
pack my suitcase.
The last time sunshine before the cold
season begins.
But first I only packed all the
toiletries I bought
for the holiday, because I
still had to wash the wet laundry before
I could pack it.
But that's taken care of now,
and I'll just do the rest shortly
before.  Because the weather
was so autumnal today, I thought
I'd make a really delicious
potato soup.
I usually look forward to my
pumpkin soups, but yes, today we're making
potato soup.  So, the
ambiance with the candles and the soup.
Oh, that gave me such a taste of autumn wheat,
I'll just say it again.  And I was just happy to be going to
bed early today, right?  After we
ate, and I really have to
say, the soup was super delicious,
I sat down on the couch with Buddy, who had also been out with
my baby earlier, to watch TV
series, and
then it was time to brush my teeth and go to
bed.  Yay.  Yes.